Jhaal
this question arises designs today in this video we will
see some photos will go to top said quiet
acid
will discuss with you some important
thing that you should do behind this and mother's life
tomorrow you should start creating your futures and options first of all
if we talk about
these east room of the so today here
Dow and S&P 500 Mukesh has been able to move and in the next
9 days celebrate 2.5 so guys if it is
corrected then tomorrow you will see the market a little then
you have to
take entry because the fruit of Nifty
is available Arun 1760
so if it is below 1768 on secret week
downloading then you will have no problem about it
because if we see today here the
market
after some consolidation for more time 30
and guys if the most emphasis is on the
colors below it because
we can see you and here below press ltd
I want you as you
can see 1778 and below it there is accused
writing and below that emphasis we have a use here  You
can do this through WhatsApp and if
you see Gu below 17018 tomorrow then we will wait and
see this kind of setup and if this
930 cycle comes up a little bit due to short covering
and then it becomes
zinc again then we will do Nagarjun here at
0608 going forward because
here before the training for tuition
starts you will
definitely get some support in the market and this
comment will remain because
Baikunth is quite strong in the bus, so
you have a meeting because of this there will be some
support in the market regarding this issue and those who should
take kerosene oil, let me tell you
because today we
fixed 37500 here and
after consolidation in the time of Rose Singh, we will
get Rs 37.50 daily, it is expected that
tomorrow's picture will be something like this, we
can add 0.5 inch from 37.10, those who believe that
if Baikunth flattens here by half an inch then
we will not give any feedback on this
until we reach 37500.  Quite
difficult to do, you can see that right now
150 is the highest, so there is trading
and below it there is also a use, because of this
we have
37500, the
16th bay dyed, the people who should take here are a
little rich
150, the next Vaikunth is 3016, so you can
definitely see 17 tests above it and
after that you can take any fresh login, so
let's see the glass which is
good for your window here and that too, what is
student photo, which is the
first stock that you need because
today and tomorrow in the trading session, America can also do a little bit
because the cost has been
in the square since October, after that the
stock Ram is creating 10 to 12 times,
if gas and within the last minute, then
a solid is still going on here, so if there
is 30,
you must subscribe
here, your peaceful
development, above this you will get profit,
Raees, the next topic is this, it belongs
to the pharmacist, so after taking the paper and consolidating from anything else,
we  Guys, today we have
seen a lot of profit booking in this topic
because the stock was announced here,
a new eye was placed on the top and
after that the staff entered a consolidation here,
but today due to the accident of a
Docomo, we need more posts, there is
more than 90 MP3 Raees, if
you
can take it and that too on the side and
after mixing it, we will move it a
little
higher. If you
like this video, then subscribe to this channel and
like and share the video
so that we can also
listen to it, the third stock is Indus Towers and
today despite the market being accurate,
we have a romantic question of one and a half inch point
because profit can be
listed here, so we will take one in it for this ascendant being the
eighth lord and that is
sense and our target will be
2014. Let me
tell you, if it
falls below, you can take it and our target
will be this challenge on this,
if you do not want to lose in the last stock, then
this stock is leg and in this topic, the
recipe here  After placing a holiday to high,
we can get a foot Hooda and officer in the stock
because the shop is
running very high and looking at the current market
performance, the profit in the stock
starts turning, so guys this thing should definitely
happen if you have a guest in Holi then
you have to chant and if possible, if
you are interested
in the sentence, if you again from 275 and
fry the stuffing, then you should place this level, then it
is fine for you and you
can withdraw the added cash in it for at least ₹500,
so that's all for today in this video,
if you have not yet subscribed to our channel, then
definitely subscribe
because we will always meet you for half an hour
and there is telegram below, if you want to
know about subscribing to get the latest updates, then
subscribe to us and you will
see the video below, of which you will
meet another video in the next video, till then
thank you so much that is
[music]